Never underestimate a nobody.
Nobody is a action, thriller film directed by Ilya Naishuller.
Hutch Mansell, a suburban dad, overlooked husband, nothing neighbor — a "nobody." When two thieves break into his home one night, Hutch's
unknown long-simmering rage is ignited and propels him on a brutal path that will uncover dark secrets he fought to leave behind.
Hutch Mansell, played by Bob Odenkirk.
Yulian Kuznetsov, played by Aleksey Serebryakov.
Becca Mansell, played by Connie Nielsen.
David Mansell, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Eddie Williams, played by Michael Ironside.
The Barber, played by Colin Salmon.
Nobody is a 2021 American action thriller film directed by
Ilya Naishuller and written by Derek Kolstad.
The film stars Bob Odenkirk as a mild-mannered family man who returns to his former life of an
assassin after he and his family become the target of a vengeful crime lord.
Connie Nielsen, RZA, Aleksei Serebryakov, and
Christopher Lloyd appear in supporting roles.
Odenkirk and David Leitch are among the film's producers.
Universal Pictures released Nobody theatrically in
the United States on March 26, 2021.
The film grossed $57 million on a $16 million budget and received generally positive reviews
from critics, who praised the action sequences and Odenkirk's performance.
A sequel, Nobody 2, was released on August 15, 2025.
The film explores themes of assassin, double life, fight,
midlife crisis, bratva (russian mafia).
The tone is dark and intense.